Guide to the Vassar College Board of Trustees Records, 1861-2014
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Board of Trustees Records
1861-2014
Vassar College. Board of Trustees
42.4 cubic feet (58 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials relating to the work of the Vassar College Board of Trustees. Includes meeting minutes, reports, correspondence, committee records, and financial records.
Administrative History
The members of the first Board of Trustees were listed in the college charter, which was passed by the New York State Legislature January 18, 1861. The first meeting of the Board occurred five weeks later on February 26th.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of materials relating to the work of the Vassar College Board of Trustees. Includes meeting minutes, reports, correspondence, committee records, and financial records.
Access
Records from roughly 1986 to the present (including all materials in boxes 24-34, 40-46, and 48-55) are currently closed to research. The rest of the collection is open for research with permission of the office of origin and in accordance with the regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library.
Related Materials
Vassar College Archives Files
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Administration
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Compact discs; Correspondence; Financial Records; Minutes (administrative records); Reports
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Trustees
Encoding Information
Encoded by Elizabeth Clarke, June 2007. Updated by Laura Streett, March 2009. Last updated by Emma Gronbeck, September 2025.
Acquisition Information
College transfer in multiple and continuing accessions. (A2001-001, A2003-001, A2003-012, A2004-011, A2004-020, A2004-021, A2005-007, A2006-002, A2006-021, A2006-044, A2007-003, A2007-004, A2007-011, A2007-012, A2007-026, A2007-059, A2007-060, A2008-004, A2008-022, A2008-026, A2008-027, A2009-006, A2009-045, A2010-005, A2010-006, A2010-008, A2011-013, A2011-035, A2011-054, A2012-016, A2012-027, A2012-030, A2013-031, A2014-027, A2014-054)
Some materials (in boxes 29-34, 53, 56-58) were transferred from the Office of the Vice President for Finance in 2007 and 2025 (A2007-046, A2025-018).
Materials from the Trustee Committee on Buildings and Grounds in boxes 48-51 were transferred in 2007 and 2009. (A2007-047, A2009-014)
Other Formats
Some minutes have been digitized and are searchable through a database. However, direct access to the database is restricted to the Special Collections staff. Please contact the staff for further information.
Series List
- Series I. Minutes and Reports, 1861-2014
- Series II. Committees, 1861-2011
- Series III. Secretary's Files, 1931-2005
  The Secretary's Files are divided into three subseries. The first set is arranged alphabetically and dates primarily from the 1940s. The second set is arranged alphabetically and dates from 1977 to 1989, and includes minutes, reports, agendas and some correspondence relating to regular meetings of the Board as well as its committees. The last set is minutes of the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees and is arranged chronologically.
- Series IV. Miscellaneous, 1868-2006
Container List
- SERIES I. MINUTES and REPORTS, 1861-2014
  - Minutes of Meetings of the Full Board, 1861-1997
    - Set 1, 1861-1934
      - Vol. 1, 1861-1891; (original) (Box 1)
      - Vol. 2, 1891-1921; (original) (Box 2)
      - Vol. 3, 1921-1934; (original) (Box 3)
    - Set 2, 1861-1945
      - Vol. 1, 1861-1891 (Box 4)
      - Vol. 2, 1892-1919 (Box 4)
      - Vol. 3, 1920-1926 (Box 5)
      - Vol. 4, 1927-1933 (Box 5)
      - Vol. 5, 1934-1939 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 6, 1940-1945 (Box 6)
    - Set 3, 1933-1997
      - Vol. 1, 1933 Oct - 1939 Jun (Box 7)
      - Vol. 2, 1939-1945 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 3, 1945-1949 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 4, 1949-1953 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 5, 1953-1958 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 6, 1958-1963 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 7, 1963-1966 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 8, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 9, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
      - Vol. 10, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
      - Vol. 11, 1972-1975 (Box 8)
      - Vol. 12, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
      - Vol. 13, 1978-1984 (Box 8)
      - Vol. 14, 1984-1989; [RESTRICTED] (Box 8)
      - Vol. 15, 1989-1997; (3 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 8)
    - Set 4, 1983-1997
      - Vol. 1, 1983 May - 1988 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Box 8)
      - Vol. 2, 1989 Oct - 1993 May; [RESTRICTED] (Box 8)
      - Vol. 3, 1993 Oct - 1997 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings, 1861-1998
    - Set 1, 1861-1925
      - Vol. 1, 1861-1870; (original) (Box 9)
      - Vol. 2, 1870-1879; (original) (Box 10)
      - Vol. 3, 1880-1901; (original, 3 folders) (Box 11)
      - Vol. 4, 1901-1915; (original) (Box 12)
      - Vol. 5, 1915-1925; (original) (Box 13)
    - Set 2, 1861-1937
      - Vol. 1, 1861 Jan - 1863 Jun (Box 14)
      - Vol. 2, 1863 Jul - 1865 Dec (Box 14)
      - Vol. 3, 1866 Jan - 1872 Jun (Box 14)
      - Vol. 4, 1872 Jul - 1879 Dec (Box 14)
      - Vol. 5, 1880 Jan - 1885 Jun (Box 14)
      - Vol. 6, 1885 Jul - 1893 Dec (Box 14)
      - Vol. 7, 1894 Jan - 1909 Dec; (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Vol. 8, 1910 Jan - 1919 Dec; (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Vol. 9, 1920 Jan - 1925 Sep; (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Vol. 10, 1925 Sep - 1932 Jul (Box 14)
      - Vol. 11, 1932 Sep - 1937 Dec (Box 14)
    - Set 3, 1938-1969
      - Vol. 1, 1938 Apr - 1956 Apr (Folders 15.1-15.3)
      - Vol. 2, 1956 Jul - 1961 Mar (Folders 15.4-15.6)
      - Vol. 3, 1961 Sep - 1964 Jun (Folders 15.7-15.10)
      - Vol. 4, 1964 Sep - 1967 Jun (Folders 15.11-15.14)
      - Vol. 5, 1967 Sep - 1969 Jun (Folders 15.14-15.17)
    - Set 4, 1932-1998
      - Vol. 1, 1932 Sep - 1939 May (Folders 15.18-15.19)
      - Vol. 2, 1939 Sep - 1946 Apr (Folder 15.20)
      - Vol. 3, 1946 Sep -1949 May (Folder 16.1)
      - Vol. 4, 1949 Jul - 1953 Apr (Folder 16.2)
      - Vol. 5, 1953 Sep - 1958 Mar (Folder 16.3)
      - Vol. 6, 1958 Sep - 1961 Mar (Folder 16.4)
      - Vol. 7, 1961 Sep - 1964 Mar (Folder 16.5)
      - Vol. 8, 1964 Sep - 1968 Jun (Folder 16.6)
      - Vol. 9, 1968 Sep - 1969 Jun (Folder 16.7)
      - Vol. 10, 1969 Sep - 1972 Jun (Folder 16.8)
      - Vol. 11, 1972 Sep - 1975 May (Folder 16.9)
      - Vol. 12, 1975 Sep - 1982 May (Folder 16.10)
      - Vol. 13, 1982 Aug - 1990 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 16.11)
      - Vol. 14, 1990 Aug - 1998 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 16.12)
  - Reports, 1926-1946
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 1, 1926-1927 (Folder 16.13)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 2, 1927-1928 (Folder 16.14)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 3, 1928-1929 (Folder 16.15)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 4, 1929-1930 (Folder 16.16)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 5, 1930-1931 (Folder 17.1)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 6, 1931-1932 (Folder 17.2)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 7, 1932-1933 (Folder 17.3)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 8, 1933-1934 (Folder 17.4)
    - Collected Reports, Vol. 9, 1934-1935 (Folder 17.5)
    - President's Reports, 1926-1946 (Folder 17.6)
  - Combined Full Board and Executive Committee Minutes and Reports, 1936-2014
    - Minutes and Reports, 1936 Sep -1938 Apr (Folder 17.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1938 May - 1939 Jun (Folder 17.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1939 Sep - 1940 Feb (Folder 17.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1940 Apr - Jun (Folder 17.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1940 Sep - 1941 Apr (Folder 17.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1941 May - Jun (Folder 17.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1941 Jul - 1942 Feb (Folder 17.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1942 Mar - Jun (Folder 17.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1942 Sep - Dec (Folder 18.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1943 Jan - Jun (Folder 18.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1943 Sep - 1944 May (Folder 18.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1944 Jun - 1945 Apr (Folder 18.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1945 May - Dec (Folder 18.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1946 Jan - Mar (Folder 18.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1946 Apr - Nov (Folder 18.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1946 Dec - 1947 Mar (Folder 18.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1947 Apr - Jun (Folder 18.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1947 Sep - 1948 Jan (Folder 18.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1948 Feb - May (Folder 18.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1948 Jun - Oct (Folder 18.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1948 Nov - 1949 Apr (Folder 18.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1949 May - Jun (Folder 18.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1949 Jul - Dec (Folder 18.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1950 Jan - Apr (Folder 18.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1950 May - Sep (Folder 18.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1950 Oct - 1951 Jan (Folder 18.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1951 Feb - May (Folder 18.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1951 Jun - Sep (Folder 19.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1951 Oct - 1952 Jan (Folder 19.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1952 Feb - May (Folder 19.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1952 Jun - Dec (Folder 19.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1953 Jan - Apr (Folder 19.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1953 May - Jun (Folder 19.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1953 Sep - 1954 Feb (Folder 19.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1954 Mar - Jun (Folder 19.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1954 Sep - Dec (Folder 19.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1955 Jan - Jun (Folder 19.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1955 Aug - Dec (Folder 19.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1956 Jan - Apr (Folder 19.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1956 May - Sep (Folder 19.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1956 Oct - 1957 Feb (Folder 19.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1957 Mar - Jun (Folder 19.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1957 Sep - Dec (Folder 19.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1958 Jan - Apr (Folder 19.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1958 May - Sep (Folder 20.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1958 Oct - 1959 Feb (Folder 20.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1959 Mar - May (Folder 20.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1959 Jun - Oct (Folder 20.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1959 Dec - 1960 Feb (Folder 20.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1960 Mar - Jul (Folder 20.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1960 Sep - Dec (Folder 20.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1961 Feb - Apr (Folder 20.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1961 May - Aug (Folder 20.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1961 Sep - Oct (Folder 20.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1961 Nov - 1962 Feb (Folder 20.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1962 Mar - May (Folder 20.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1962 Jun (Folder 20.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1962 Sep - Nov (Folder 20.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1962 Dec - 1963 Feb (Folder 20.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1963 Mar - May (Folder 20.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1963 Jun - Sep (Folder 20.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1963 Oct - 1964 Feb (Folder 21.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1964 Mar - May (Folder 21.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1964 Jun - Sep (Folder 21.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1964 Oct - Dec (Folder 21.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1965 Jan - May (Folder 21.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1965 Jun - Sep (Folder 21.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1965 Oct - Nov (Folder 21.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1965 Dec - 1966 Mar (Folder 21.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1966 Apr - Jun (Folder 21.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1966 Sep - Dec (Folder 21.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1967 Jan - Mar (Folder 21.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1967 Apr - Jun (Folder 21.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1967 Jun - Sep (Folder 21.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1967 Oct - 1968 Feb (Folder 21.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1968 Mar - May (Folder 21.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1968 Jun - Jul (Folder 21.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1968 Sep - Oct (Folder 22.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1968 Nov - Dec (Folder 22.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 Jan - Feb (Folder 22.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 Mar - Apr (Folder 22.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 May - Aug (Folder 22.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 Sep (Folder 22.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 Oct - Nov (Folder 22.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 Dec - 1970 Jan (Folder 22.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1970 Feb - Apr (Folder 22.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1970 May - Aug (Folder 22.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1970 Sep - Dec (Folder 22.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1971 Jan - Apr (Folder 22.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1971 May - Sep (Folder 22.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1971 Oct - 1972 Apr (Folder 22.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1972 May - Jun (Folder 22.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1972 Oct - 1973 Mar (Folder 22.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1973 Apr - Oct (Folder 22.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1973 Nov - 1974 Jun (Folder 22.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1974 Sep - 1975 May (Folder 23.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1975 Jun - Dec (Folder 23.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1976 Jan - Jun (Folder 23.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1976 Sep (Folder 23.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1976 Oct - 1977 Feb (Folder 23.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1977 Mar - Sep (Folder 23.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1977 Oct - 1978 Apr (Folder 23.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1978 May - Dec (Folder 23.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1979 Jan - May (Folder 23.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1979 Sep - Dec; [empty] (Folder 23.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1980 Feb (Folder 23.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1980 May (Folder 23.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1980 Oct (Folder 23.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1980 Dec (Folders 23.14-23.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1981 Feb (Folder 23.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1981 May (Folder 23.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1981 Oct (Folder 23.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1981 Dec (Folder 23.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1982 Feb (Folder 23.20)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1982 May (Folder 23.21)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1982 Oct (Folder 23.22)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1982 Dec (Folder 23.23)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1983 Feb (Folder 23.24)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1983 May (Folder 23.25)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1983 Oct (Folder 23.26)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1983 Dec (Folder 23.27)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1984 Feb (Folder 23.28)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1984 May (Folder 23.29)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1984 Oct (Folder 23.30)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1984 Dec (Folder 23.31)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1985 Feb (Folder 23.32)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1985 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 24.1-24.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1985 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1986 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1986 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1986 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1987 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1987 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1987 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1988 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1988 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 24.11-24.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1988 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1989 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1989 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1989 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1990 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1990 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1990 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1991 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.20)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1991 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.21)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1991 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.22)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1992 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 24.23)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1992 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1992 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1993 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1993 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1993 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1994 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1994 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1994 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1995 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1995 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1995 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1996 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1996 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1996 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.14)
    - Minutes and Reports (with notes and additions), 1997 Feb - 2006 May; (29 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 58)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1997 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1997 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1997 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1998 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1998 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1998 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.20)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1999 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.21)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1999 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.22)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1999 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.23)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2000 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 25.24)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2000 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2000 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2001 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2001 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2001 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2002 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2002 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2002 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.8)
    - Minutes and Reports - Special Campaign Session, 2002 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2003 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2003 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2003 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 26.12-26.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2004 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2004 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2004 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2005 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.17)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2005 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2005 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 26.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2006 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 26.20-26.21)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2006 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 26.22-26.23)
    - Minutes and Reports - Executive Committee Meeting, 2006 Aug; [RESTRICTED] (Box 58)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2006 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 27.1-27.2)
    - Minutes and Reports - Executive Committee Meetings, 2007 Feb - 2009 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Box 58)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2007 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2007 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2007 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 27.5-27.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2007 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.7)
    - Minutes and Reports - Retreat, 2008 Feb-Mar; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2008 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.9)
    - Minutes and Reports - Executive Committee Meeting, 2008 Sep; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2008 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2009 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.12)
    - Minutes and Reports - Executive Committee Meeting, 2009 Sep; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2009 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.14)
    - Minutes and Reports - Special Meeting, 2009 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2010 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.16)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2010 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 27.17-27.18)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2010 Sep; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.19)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2010 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.20)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2010 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.21)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2011 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.22)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2011 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.23)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2011 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.24)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2011 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.25)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2012 Feb; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 27.26)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2012 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2012 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2012 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2013 Mar; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2013 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2013 Sep; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2013 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2013 Dec; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2014 Feb-Mar; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2014 May; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 2014 Oct; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 28.11)
- SERIES II. TRUSTEE COMMITTEES, 1861-2011
  - Audit Committee, 1981-2002; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 29.1)
  - Audit Committee, 1981 Oct - 2011 Feb; (5 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 56)
  - Budget Committee, 1958-1989; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 29.2-29.12)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 1989-2002; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 29.13-29.19)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 1998-2010; (5 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 56)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1925-2002; [RESTRICTED] (Folders 30.1-30.9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1991 May - 2010 Dec; (4 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 56)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Alumnae House - Restoration and Mechanical Upgrade," pre-schematic plans, 1994 Nov 21; [RESTRICTED] (Box 54)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Avery Courtyard Proposal - Center for Drama and Film" by Balmori Associates, concept art, circa 2000; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 52.1)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Avery Hall" by Cesar Pelli & Associates, architectural plans, 1994 Mar 29; (11 leaves) [RESTRICTED] (Box 53)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Avery Hall" by Cesar Pelli & Associates, architectural plans, 1999 Dec 6; (10 boards) [RESTRICTED] (Box 53)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — Capital Project Executive Summary, 2000 Oct 13; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 52.2)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — Capital Project Executive Summary, 2000-2001; (2 folders) [RESTRICTED] (Box 56)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — Chicago Hall Expansion, architectural plans, undated; (6 boards) [RESTRICTED] (Box 55 (Oversize))
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Deffered Maintenance Phaseout Program Status Report", 1990 Feb 23; [RESTRICTED] (Box 56)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "The Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center," architectural plans, 1989; (5 boards) [RESTRICTED] (Box 48)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "The Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center," architectural plans, photographs, and report, 1989-1990; (10 boards) [RESTRICTED] (Box 49)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "The Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center - Sculpture Garden" by Balmori Associates, undated; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 52.3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Jewett House Renovation Plans" by Herbert S. Newman and Partners, 2002 Mar; [RESTRICTED] (Box 54)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "The Renovation and Renewal of Jewett House" by Herbert S. Newman and Partners, 2002 Oct; (3 copies) [RESTRICTED] (Folder 52.4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Kenyon Hall Renovation Design Development" by Gluckman Mayner Architects, 2002 Jun; [RESTRICTED] (Box 54)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee — "Kenyon Hall Renovation" by Gluckman Mayner Architects, 2002 Oct 11; (3 copies) [RESTRICTED] (Box 54)